Can I talk to you?
Yes.
There is an embarrassment in your life.
Do you know what I mean by an embarrassment?
Something you cannot tell anyone.
It is something you don't want anyone to know.
It's only you.
You keep it to yourself and you don't want people to know.
Yes, sir.
Do you want me to mention it?
No
I should not mention it?
No, let us put shame to satan.
Bedwetting.
Yes, sir.
You just sleep and you see yourself wetting the bed.
As I am saying it, it is gone.
It is gone.
Father, thank You, Lord.
In Jesus Christ's name.
Amen
TESTIMONY TIME
Emmanuel!
(God with us - Matthew 1:23)
People of God, I have good news to share.
My name is Elysia Straub. I come from the United States.
Who is the sister besides you here?
This here is my beautiful mother Galina.
Last week, Prophet T.B. Joshua gave me a prophecy.
He walked up to me and said, "Sister, you have something that you don't want to share with anyone.
You have a secret".
I know, I didn't say yes.
He said that it was a generational curse, which was bedwetting.
Afterwards, he placed his hand upon me.
I fell to the ground. I felt released, free.
I felt the Holy Spirit inside of me.
Tell us more about this problem of bedwetting, how it started and how it really affected your life negatively?
I had this problem of bedwetting since childhood.
Every time I went to other peoples' places, I'd feel ashamed about it.
I felt isolated, rejected. I felt that I was not accepted for who I am.
This is something that has been happening to you right from childhood that you have been bedwetting.
Yes, sir.
Explain to us - each time it happened, how did it affect you negatively - both socially and
in terms of your relationship with others? How did it make you feel?
Normally when I would go to sleep - I am usually a light sleeper -
every time before the middle of the night, when I slept very deeply, I felt like someone was holding me down.
It won't let me go. The only time when I'd wake up is when I felt wet.
I felt ashamed, so I kept it as a secret from others.
I felt isolated. I didn't want to be with anyone else after this happened. I felt guilty inside.
You mentioned at the beginning that this was actually a generational curse.
Can you explain more about how this affected the whole family?
I wasn't the only one; I also had a family member,
who's my uncle and also had this issue. He felt very ashamed of it.
So did my other family members, such as my little cousins.
As a young lady looking ahead to the future,
how did you feel knowing that you had this problem in terms of moving forward in life,
maybe wanting to get married later on?
How did it make you feel knowing that you had this terrible secret?
I felt that there was no hope for me.
I thought about what would happen to me in the future, "Will this continue,
will I get married, will my children and my children's children have the same generational curse?"
We really understand from our sister how serious this problem of bedwetting was.
You said that you kept this as a secret, is that right?
Yes, sir.
Wow. Tell us - how did you come to hear about The SCOAN
and actually be here today in the presence of God.
I heard about The SCOAN through family members.
They knew I had this problem, so they told my mother, and we also watched the YouTube videos.
OK, so you learned about the ministry and thank God you came here.
Tell us - how did you feel last week, when the man of God, Prophet T.B. Joshua approached you
and gave you this word of prophecy, something you did not disclose to him -
a secret that you kept, that only you and your family members knew about.
How did you feel when this word of prophecy was given?
When he first came up to me...
During screening, when I was supposed to write down my problems, I did not add bedwetting.
When the Prophet came up to me, he said exactly what I should have put on the placard.
I was so shocked; this was exactly why I came here - to be freed from this curse.
Let's put our hands together for Jesus Christ!
I hope we understand our sister.
She said that when she was asked about her problems before,
she was too ashamed to even mention bedwetting on her placard
when it was time for her to go to the prayer line.
But God, through Prophet T.B. Joshua revealed exactly what her problem was
and that word of prophecy is what we are seeing on the screen here.
Sister, we saw Prophet T.B. Joshua praying for you and you fell to the ground.
What happened when he prayed for you, what were your experiences?
I felt released. I felt lighter. I felt free in Jesus' mighty name.
Wow. Ever since that prayer and that prophecy, tell us your experiences.
Ever since that day happened, I have been free, I have been dry on my bed,
I feel enlightened, happy and joyful.
Let's put our hands together for Jesus Christ!
You said before that in your sleep, you felt something pressing you down,
a nightmare attacking you, pressing you down, until you woke up and found the bed wet.
Tell us - after this deliverance and prophecy, what have been your experiences in your dreams?
Have you had such experiences repeat itself?
It's been dry. I don't feel anyone pushing me down anymore.
I felt like the Holy Spirit is lifting me up, that I am free completely.
One more time, let's put our hands together for our Lord Jesus Christ!
What a miraculous wonderful testimony!
As the Prophet said during that prophecy, "As I say it now, it is finished".
Because indeed that word of prophecy contains both healing and deliverance.
It's a package that has both the question and answer.
We can see the evidence right now in the life of our sister.
Immediately after that prophetic message, she has not bedwetted again.
She is completely free from that terrible scourge of bedwetting right from her childhood.
Sister, what is your advice to people of God watching you right now?
My advice to everyone is to have hope. Never lose hope.
When you are facing a situation like this or any situation, it is not impossible with God.
He is not done with you. He is still continuing and has a plan for you.
Amen!
Amen! Let's put our hands together for Jesus Christ!
Glory be to God. Now we just want to quickly hear from the sister beside you as well.
Sister, you are welcome. Just tell us your name, and where you are from.
My name is Galina Straub. I am from the United States.
Who is this sister beside you? Who is she to you?
This is my daughter, Elysia Straub.
Tell us on your own side - what can you say about the problem she was having,
how it really affected the whole family.
We had a generational curse in my family.
It passed on to her. She had been bedwetting since she was a child.
We have been praying, fasting for her and taking her to doctors.
They said she should be able to grow out of it but she never did.
How did you feel each time you saw that she was bedwetting?
Even at her age, how did that make you feel as someone very close to her?
I felt the shame. I felt bad for her and felt bad for me.
Like what did I do wrong? Why is this on her?
Did I do something wrong or maybe I should do something about it?
We tried everything we could but we did not have any results.
You were here last week when Prophet T.B. Joshua gave her that word of prophecy.
How did you feel as the prophecy was given to her?
I almost cried because this was exactly what we came here for.
She was ashamed; she didn't want to write things out.
He said exactly the words that she didn't want anybody to know.
This is the truth.
The Prophet said exactly what she had.
After the prophecy came, I knew that God had a plan for us.
I believe that this curse will be broken.
Glory be to God Almighty. Since that word of prophecy and deliverance that came with it,
how has she been doing since then? How is her condition right now?
It has been great. I have been checking every day and night on her.
She's able to get up on her own to go to the bathroom.
She has been dry. I just want to thank God.
He is the same yesterday, today, and forever. He is still healing and delivering.
I just want to praise God for this church, and for Prophet T.B. Joshua.
Thank you. Thank you so much. We really really appreciate it.
Let us put our hands together for our Lord Jesus Christ!
Glory be to God. Indeed there are no natural words to describe it, except to say, "Thank You, Jesus!".
Finally, what is your word of advice to viewers around the world watching you right now?
My advice is to believe and trust in God.
His word is the same yesterday and today. Whatever He promises, He does it.
You just have to look for it.
I know this church is a great church. We see the result.
Keep praying and keep believing.
Come here, use the Anointing Water, anything you can do to get your deliverance, to get your answer.
Amen. Thank You, Jesus. We want to encourage this family now that Jesus Christ has intervened in this case,
continue to make the Word of God the standard for your lives.
We know the best is yet to come as you do so in Jesus' mighty name.
Amen.
We believe you have been inspired by the clip you have just watched.
Click here to subscribe, to witness more of God's power at work in our generation today
and stay up-to-date with the latest prophecies, deliverances,
sermons and testimonies from The SCOAN.
Emmanuel TV - Changing Lives, Changing Nations, and Changing the World.
CR Robert Begier 25/04/2019